Now that you've selected your tea cup I'm going to show you how to prep it so we're able to make a nice little design in here.
First of all we're going to remove the cup and this is called cling.
It's a very, very sticky tape and what this will do is secure your tea cup to the plate.
You just rip off a little piece and you can pull it out and just kind of go around the little the circle on the plate and then you take your tea cup and stick it to the plate.
And you don't want any of it to show so, there we go.
So that's how your get this to stick.
Next we're going to take a piece of floral foam, now the floral foam I have had soaking, it's best to let this soak overnight because you don't want it to have pockets of air in here.
So if it soaks overnight it's going to be very moist you want it to be saturated fully.
And what I'm going to do is cut a piece to fit in this container.
So I'm just going to cut a little piece and we're going to just cut it down a little bit more, and a little bit more, just going to kind of wing it here, then you push it in to the container.
Next you tape the container you just use your clear florist tape and just make a little X on the container.
O.K. and that's how you prep the container.